/**This is where all the questions for the quiz are stored. Each quiz category has an array where the questions
 * are stored as dictionaries.
 */

// Here is where the questions for the geography quiz are stored
let geographyQuestions = [
    {
        question: 'Which country has the largest landmass in the world?',
        answers: ['Russia', 'China', 'Canada', 'United States of America'],
        correctAnswer: 'Russia'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which is the largest country in South America?',
        answers: ['Columbia', 'Brazil', 'Argentina', 'Peru'],
        correctAnswer: 'Brazil'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which city is the capital of Australia?',
        answers: ['Melbourne', 'Perth', 'Sydney', 'Canberra'],
        correctAnswer: 'Sydney'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which is the largest city in the world based on surface area?',
        answers: ['Hulunbuir', 'Mumbai', 'Shanghai', 'New York'],
        correctAnswer: 'Hulunbuir'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which river runs through Paris?',
        answers: ['Danube', 'Elbe', 'Thames', 'Seine'],
        correctAnswer: 'Seine'
    },
    {
        question: 'In which country is the region of Transilvania located?',
        answers: ['Croatia', 'Moldavia', 'Romania', 'Albania'],
        correctAnswer: 'Romania'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which country is NOT part of the Scaninavian Peninsula?',
        answers: ['Finlad', 'Denmark', 'Sweden', 'Norway'],
        correctAnswer: 'Denmark'
    },
    {
        question: 'In which body of water is the Isle of Man located?',
        answers: ['The Irish Sea', 'The North Sea', 'The Atlantic Ocean', 'The English Channel'],
        correctAnswer: 'The Irish Sea'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which is Earth\'s largest continent?',
        answers: ['Asia', 'Africa', 'Australia', 'Antarctica'],
        correctAnswer: 'Asia'
    },
    {
        question: 'What percentage of the River Nile is located in Egypt?',
        answers: ['9%', '86%', '22%', '100%'],
        correctAnswer: '22%'
    },
]

let scienceQuestions = [
    {
        question: 'Question number 1 (index 0)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: 'd'
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 2 (index 1)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 3 (index 2)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 4 (index 3)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 5 (index 4)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 6 (index 5)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 7 (index 6)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 8 (index 7)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 9 (index 8)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 10 (index 9)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
]

let musicQuestions = [
    {
        question: 'Question number 1 (index 0)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: 'd'
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 2 (index 1)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 3 (index 2)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 4 (index 3)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 5 (index 4)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 6 (index 5)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 7 (index 6)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 8 (index 7)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 9 (index 8)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 10 (index 9)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
]

let animalsQuestions = [
    {
        question: 'Question number 1 (index 0)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: 'd'
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 2 (index 1)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 3 (index 2)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 4 (index 3)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 5 (index 4)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 6 (index 5)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 7 (index 6)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 8 (index 7)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 9 (index 8)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Question number 10 (index 9)',
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
]

